{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ko.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269177007","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269177007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_kwako_ambako_yuko"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269183004","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269183004"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 29a83420-7897-4138-ad0b-7f0c24433089"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269184569","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269184568"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 29a83420-7897-4138-ad0b-7f0c24433089"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269184636","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269184636"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 29a83420-7897-4138-ad0b-7f0c24433089"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ko.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269195503","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269195503"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 29a83420-7897-4138-ad0b-7f0c24433089"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269199926","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269199925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 29a83420-7897-4138-ad0b-7f0c24433089"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269210700","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269210700"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" babako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269211735","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269211734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" babako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKO"," userResponse":" BABAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269214506","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269214506"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKO"," userResponse":" KWAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269214902","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269214902"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269215678","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269215678"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ambako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" AMBAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269218558","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269218558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ambako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" AMBAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269221788","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269221788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269222818","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269222818"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKO"," userResponse":" ZAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269227014","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269227014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269228053","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269228053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269231419","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269231419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" soko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269232466","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269232466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" soko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOKO"," userResponse":" SOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269235746","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269235746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiboko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269236810","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269236810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiboko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269239675","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269239675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKO"," userResponse":" KIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269241465","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269241465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKO"," userResponse":" KIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269244723","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269244722"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msisimko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSISIMKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269245760","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269245760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msisimko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSISIMKO"," userResponse":" MSISIMKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ko.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269249828","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269249828"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" msisimko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269249981","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269249981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113245"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msisimko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSISIMKO"," userResponse":" MSISIMKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}